<resources>
    <string name="app_name">intery</string>
    <string name="prefs_file">com.albaburdallo.intery.PREFERENCE_FILE_KEY</string>
    <string name="or">or</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="delete">Are you sure you want to delete?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="register"><b>Register here</b></string>
    <string name="noAcc">Don\'t have an account yet?</string>
    <string name="logIn">Log in</string>
    <string name="logInGoogle">Log in with Google</string>
    <string name="logInEmail">Email</string>
    <string name="logInPassword">Password</string>
    <string name="signIn">Sign in</string>
    <string name="logOut"><b><i>Log out</i></b></string>
    <string name="createAcc"><b>New account</b></string>
    <string name="name"><b>Name</b></string>
    <string name="surname"><b>Surname</b></string>
    <string name="email"><b>Email</b></string>
    <string name="password"><b>Password</b></string>
    <string name="repeat_password"><b>Repeat password</b></string>
    <string name="termsAndConditions">You must accept the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="hello">¡Hi, </string>
    <string name="noTasks"><i>No tasks</i></string>
    <string name="create_task">New task</string>
    <string name="addTask"><b>New task</b></string>
    <string name="taskName">Title (Ex: Dinner with mom)</string>
    <string name="taskStart">Start</string>
    <string name="taskEnd">End</string>
    <string name="taskDate">Date</string>
    <string name="taskTime">Time</string>
    <string name="taskAllDay">All day</string>
    <string name="taskRemindMe">Remind me</string>
    <string name="taskNotes">Notes</string>
    <string name="taskDateValidation">Start date must be prior to the end date</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="userError">Something went wrong while authenticating the user</string>
    <string name="tasksOption"><b><i>Tasks</i></b></string>
    <string name="walletOption"><b><i>Wallet</i></b></string>
    <string name="habitOption"><b><i>Habits</i></b></string>
    <string name="settingsOption"><b><i>Settings</i></b></string>
    <string name="myCalendars"><b>My calendars</b></string>
    <string name="noCalendars">No calendars</string>
    <string name="create_calendar">New calendar</string>
    <string name="create_calendar_title"><b><i>New calendar</i></b></string>
    <string name="calendarTitle">Title (Ex: Work)</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="calendarDescription">Description (Ex: Task for working)</string>
    <string name="calendarColor">Color</string>
    <string name="remainingTasks">tasks remaining</string>
    <string name="calendarValidation">You must select a calendar</string>
    <string name="select">-- Select --</string>
    <string name="selectEntity">Select an entity</string>
    <string name="selectSection">Select a section</string>
    <string name="deleteCalendar">Deleting the calendar will delete all of its tasks, do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="seeMore"><i>See more...</i></string>
    <string name="noTasksForToday"><i>No tasks for today</i></string>
    <string name="addTransaction">Add transaction</string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
    <string name="expenditures">Expenditures</string>
    <string name="incomes">Incomes</string>
    <string name="noTransactions">No transactions</string>
    <string name="cantDeleteCalendar">Cannot delete this calendar</string>
    <string name="defaultCalendar">Default calendar</string>
    <string name="exisitingCalendar">This calendar already exists</string>
    <string name="nothing_here">Nothing here…</string>
    <string name="newTransaction"><b><i>New transaction</i></b></string>
    <string name="expenditure">Expenditure</string>
    <string name="income">Income</string>
    <string name="transactionQuantity">Quantity (Ex: 16.50)</string>
    <string name="transactionConcept">Concept (Ex: Clothes)</string>
    <string name="transactionDate">Date</string>
    <string name="transactionNotes">Notes</string>
    <string name="addEntity">Add entity</string>
    <string name="addSection">Add section</string>
    <string name="entityExists">This entity already exists</string>
    <string name="sectionExists">This section already exists</string>
    <string name="createEntity"><b><i>Create entity</i></b></string>
    <string name="createSection"><b><i>Create section</i></b></string>
    <string name="validateEntity">You must select an entity</string>
    <string name="validateSection">You must select a section</string>
    <string name="totalSavings">This month you have saved: </string>
    <string name="totalNoSavings">This month you have spent: </string>
    <string name="totalSpent">Total spent</string>
    <string name="totalReceived">Total received</string>
    <string name="totalZero">Total money cannot be less than 0</string>
    <string name="fiveMinutes">5 minutes before</string>
    <string name="halfHour">30 minutes before</string>
    <string name="oneHour">1 hour before</string>
    <string name="atTheMoment">At the moment</string>
    <string name="oneDay">1 day before</string>
    <string name="inFiveMinutes">In 5 minutes</string>
    <string name="inThrirtyMinutes">In 30 minutes</string>
    <string name="inOneHour">In 1 hour</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="tomorrow">Tomorrow</string>
    <string name="snooze">Snooze</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="editProfile">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="changePassword">Change password</string>
    <string name="oldPassword">Old password</string>
    <string name="newPassword">New password</string>
    <string name="repeatNewPassword">Repeat new password</string>
    <string name="passUpdated">Password updated</string>
    <string name="forgotPass">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="resetEmail">An email was sent to restart your password</string>
    <string name="oldPassNotValid">Your old password is not correct</string>
    <string name="fileError">An error ocurred uploading the file</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="cantEditEmail">The email cannot be edited</string>
    <string name="myHabits">My habits</string>
    <string name="noHabits">No habits</string>
    <string name="newHabit">New habit</string>
    <string name="started">Started:</string>
    <string name="habitName">Title (Ex: Go running)</string>
    <string name="habitReminder">Reminder</string>
    <string name="habitNotes">Notes</string>
    <string name="habitColor">Color:</string>
    <string name="goal">Goal:</string>
    <string name="habitRemind">Time of reminder</string>
    <string name="everyDay">Every day</string>
    <string name="twoAWeek">Two days in a week</string>
    <string name="oneAWeek">One day in a week</string>
    <string name="oneAMonth">One day in a month</string>
    <string name="twoAMonth">Two days in a month</string>
    <string name="threeWeek">Three days in a week</string>
    <string name="threeMonth">Three days in a month</string>
    <string name="habitDateValidator">End date must be later than today</string>
    <string name="editHabit">Edit habit</string>
    <string name="editTask">Edit task</string>
    <string name="editTransaction">Edit transaction</string>
    <string name="exisitingHabit">This habit already exists</string>
    <string name="habitNotificationBody">Have you completed your habit yet?</string>
    <string name="populateTaskName1">Dinner with mom</string>
    <string name="populateTaskDesc1">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="populateTaskName2">Maria\'s birthday</string>
    <string name="populateSection1">Subscriptions</string>
    <string name="populateTransactionName">Maria\'s birthday groceries</string>
    <string name="populateEntityName">Target</string>
    <string name="populateSection2">Groceries</string>
    <string name="populateEntity3">Anna</string>
    <string name="populateTransactionName2">Bizum for dinner</string>
    <string name="populateHabitName">Meditate</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settingsLanguage">Language</string>
    <string name="settingsCurrency">Currency</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="serviceConditions">Service conditions</string>
    <string name="legalNotice">Legal notice</string>
    <string name="privacySettings">Privacy settings</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="nonEmptyValidation">Can\'t be empty</string>
    <string name="equalToValidation">Passwords must match</string>
    <string name="loginError">An error has occurred. Please check your email and password</string>
    <string name="alertError">An error occurred while registering the user</string>
    <string name="entityName">Name (Ex: SheIn)</string>
    <string name="sectionName">Name (Ex: Shopping)</string>
    <string name="donePopup">DONE</string>
    <string name="terminos_y_condiciones">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="acepto_los">I accept the</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"><p>Date last updated: 27/05/2021</p>
        <p>In accordance with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (General Data Protection Regulation - GDPR), Intery, informs users of the Intery application (hereinafter the Application), about the processing of personal data, which they have voluntarily provided during the process of registration, access and use of the service. </p>
        <ol>
            <li><p><strong>IDENTIFICATION OF THE DATA CONTROLLER </strong>.</p>
                <p>Intery is the entity responsible for the processing of the data provided by the customers of the Application (hereinafter, the User(s)).</p>
            </li>
            <li><p><strong>PURPOSE OF THE DATA PROCESSING </strong>.</p>
                <p>In order to proceed with the registration, access and subsequent use of the Application, the User must provide - on a voluntary basis - personal data (essentially, identification and contact data), which will be incorporated into automated supports owned by Intery.</p>
            </li>
        </ol>
        <p>The collection, storage, modification, structuring and, if necessary, elimination of the data provided by the Users, will constitute processing operations carried out by the Responsible Party, with the purpose of guaranteeing the correct functioning of the Application, maintaining the service and/or commercial relationship with the User, and for the management, administration, information, provision and improvement of the service. </p>
        <p>The personal data provided by the User -especially the electronic mail or e-mail- may also be used to send newsletters, as well as commercial communications of promotions and/or advertising of the Application, provided that the User has previously given his express consent to receive these communications electronically. </p>
        <ol>
            <li>**LEGITIMACY</li>
        </ol>
        <p>The processing of the User\'s data is carried out with the following legal bases that legitimize the same: </p>
        <ul>
            <li>The request for information and/or the contracting of the services of the Application, whose terms and conditions will be made available to the User in any case, in advance, for their express acceptance. </li>
            <li>The free, specific, informed and unequivocal consent of the User, making available to him/her the present privacy policy, which he/she must accept by means of a statement or a clear affirmative action, such as marking a box provided for this purpose.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>In the event that the User does not provide Intery with his/her data, or does so erroneously or incompletely, it will not be possible to proceed with the use of the Application.</p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>PRESERVATION OF PERSONAL DATA </strong>. </li>
        </ol>
        <p>The personal data provided by the User will be kept in the systems and databases of the Data Controller, as long as the User continues to use the Application, and as long as the User does not request its deletion. </p>
        <p>In order to purge the possible responsibilities derived from the treatment, the data will be conserved for a minimum period of five years.</p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>RECIPIENTS</strong>.</li>
        </ol>
        <p>The data will not be communicated to any third party external to Intery, unless required by law or, in any case, upon request of the User\'s consent. </p>
        <p>On the other hand, Intery may give access to or transmit the personal data provided by the User to third party service providers, with whom it has signed data processing agreements, and who only access such information in order to provide a service for and on behalf of the Controller. </p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>DATA RETENTION. </strong></li>
        </ol>
        <p>Inery, informs the User that, as a data hosting service provider and in accordance with the provisions of Law 34/2002 of July 11, 2002 on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce (LSSI), retains for a maximum period of 12 months the information necessary to identify the origin of the hosted data and the time at which the service was initiated.</p>
        <p> The retention of this data does not affect the secrecy of communications and may only be used in the framework of a criminal investigation or for the safeguarding of public security, being made available to judges and/or courts or the Ministry that so requires. </p>
        <p>The communication of data to the State Security Forces and Corps will be made in accordance with the provisions of the regulations on the protection of personal data, and with the utmost respect for the same. </p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>PROTECTION OF THE HOSTED INFORMATION</strong>.</li>
        </ol>
        <p>The Data Controller, takes the necessary measures to ensure the security, integrity and confidentiality of the data in accordance with the provisions of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data. </p>
        <p>Although the Responsible Party, makes backup copies of the content hosted on its servers, however it is not responsible for the accidental loss or accidental deletion of data by Users. Likewise, it does not guarantee the total replacement of data deleted by Users, since such data may have been deleted and/or modified during the period of time elapsed since the last backup. </p>
        <p>The services provided or rendered through the Application, except for specific backup services, do not include the replacement of the contents kept in the backup copies made by the Data Controller, when this loss is attributable to the User; in this case, a fee will be determined according to the complexity and volume of the recovery, always with the prior acceptance of the User. The replacement of deleted data is only included in the price of the service when the loss of the content is due to causes attributable to the Controller. </p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>EXERCISE OF RIGHTS. </strong></li>
        </ol>
        <p>Intery, informs the User that he/she has the rights of access, rectification, limitation, suppression, opposition and portability, which can be exercised by sending a request to electrónico:intery@gmail.com.</p>
        <p> Likewise, the User has the right to revoke the consent initially given, and to file claims of rights before the Spanish Data Protection Agency (AEPD). </p>
        <ol>
            <li><strong>COMMERCIAL COMMUNICATIONS BY ELECTRONIC MEANS </strong>. </li>
        </ol>
        <p>In application of the LSSI (Law of Services of the Information Society), Intery, will not send advertising or promotional communications by email or other means of electronic communication equivalent that had not been previously requested or expressly authorized by the recipients thereof.</p>
        <p>In the case of users with whom there is a previous contractual, legal or service relationship, the Data Controller is authorized to send commercial communications concerning products or services of the Data Controller that are similar to those that were initially contracted with the customer. </p>
        <p>In the event that the User wishes to unsubscribe from receiving the aforementioned communications, he/she may do so by sending an e-mail to the following address: intery@gmail.com</p>
    </string>
    <string name="terms_conditions"><p>These terms and conditions (&quot;Agreement&quot;) set forth the general terms and conditions of your use of the &quot;Intery&quot; mobile application (&quot;Mobile Application&quot; or &quot;Service&quot;) and any of its related products and services (collectively, &quot;Services&quot;). This Agreement is legally binding between you (&quot;User&quot;, &quot;you&quot; or &quot;your&quot;) and this Mobile Application developer (&quot;Operator&quot;, &quot;we&quot;, &quot;us&quot; or &quot;our&quot;). By accessing and using the Mobile Application and Services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. If you are entering into this Agreement on behalf of a business or other legal entity, you represent that you have the authority to bind such entity to this Agreement, in which case the terms &quot;User&quot;, &quot;you&quot; or &quot;your&quot; shall refer to such entity. If you do not have such authority, or if you do not agree with the terms of this Agreement, you must not accept this Agreement and may not access and use the Mobile Application and Services. You acknowledge that this Agreement is a contract between you and the Operator, even though it is electronic and is not physically signed by you, and it governs your use of the Mobile Application and Services.</p>
<h2>Accounts and membership</h2>
<p>If you create an account in the Mobile Application, you are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with it. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review new accounts before you may sign in and start using the Services. Providing false contact information of any kind may result in the termination of your account. You must immediately notify us of any unauthorized uses of your account or any other breaches of security. We will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions. We may suspend, disable, or delete your account (or any part thereof) if we determine that you have violated any provision of this Agreement or that your conduct or content would tend to damage our reputation and goodwill. If we delete your account for the foregoing reasons, you may not re-register for our Services. We may block your email address and Internet protocol address to prevent further registration.</p>
<h2>User content</h2>
<p>We do not own any data, information or material (collectively, &quot;Content&quot;) that you submit in the Mobile Application in the course of using the Service. You shall have sole responsibility for the accuracy, quality, integrity, legality, reliability, appropriateness, and intellectual property ownership or right to use of all submitted Content. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review the Content in the Mobile Application submitted or created using our Services by you. You grant us permission to access, copy, distribute, store, transmit, reformat, display and perform the Content of your user account solely as required for the purpose of providing the Services to you. Without limiting any of those representations or warranties, we have the right, though not the obligation, to, in our own sole discretion, refuse or remove any Content that, in our reasonable opinion, violates any of our policies or is in any way harmful or objectionable. Unless specifically permitted by you, your use of the Mobile Application and Services does not grant us the license to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish or distribute the Content created by you or stored in your user account for commercial, marketing or any similar purpose.</p>
<h2>Backups</h2>
<p>We perform regular backups of the Content and will do our best to ensure completeness and accuracy of these backups. In the event of the hardware failure or data loss we will restore backups automatically to minimize the impact and downtime.</p>
    <h2>Links to other resources</h2>
<p>Although the Mobile Application and Services may link to other resources (such as websites, mobile applications, etc.), we are not, directly or indirectly, implying any approval, association, sponsorship, endorsement, or affiliation with any linked resource, unless specifically stated herein. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any businesses or individuals or the content of their resources. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services, and content of any other third parties. You should carefully review the legal statements and other conditions of use of any resource which you access through a link in the Mobile Application and Services. Your linking to any other off-site resources is at your own risk.</p>
<h2>Changes and amendments</h2>
<p>We reserve the right to modify this Agreement or its terms relating to the Mobile Application and Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement in the Mobile Application. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Continued use of the Mobile Application and Services after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.</p>
<h2>Acceptance of these terms</h2>
<p>You acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By accessing and using the Mobile Application and Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to access or use the Mobile Application and Services. This terms and conditions policy was created with the <a target="_blank" href="https://www.websitepolicies.com/terms-and-conditions-generator">terms and conditions generator</a>.</p>
<h2>Contacting us</h2>
<p>If you would like to contact us to understand more about this Agreement or wish to contact us concerning any matter relating to it, you may send an email to i&#110;&#116;&#101;&#114;&#121;&#64;g&#109;&#97;il.&#99;o&#109;.</p>
<p>This document was last updated on May 27, 2021</p></string>
</resources>